<?xml version="1.0"?>
<RECORDS>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Cat care centre                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   
Call notes:     
filled up all borchure holders, nurses liked the stand loads!! Staff had a few questions.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         </text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>001A8F53-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>9FA900AB-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
Good catchup meeting with Mat, he has been away for the last few weeks and Tara has been locuming. Clinic is doing well. Asked about Simplicef and advised should be in over this/next week but will confirm. Good chance to use up their Rylexine etc though. Check on clinic materials, need more reminder cards. Updated me on local Welly vets business, very interesting discussion. Discussed feline vaccination protocols, still unsure about extending but ok to use F3 annually for now. Still not interested in focussing on FIV. 
Order materials.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            </text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>001A8F53-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>0478E6A6-BFDC-DF11-AF39-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
go over periovac, find out potential for getting cat vaccines                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                     
Call notes:     
liked idea of periovac, not motivated to order though. left material so could think about it. asked about impact of Jansens, doesnt think it will at this stage. offered free rev with kitten vaccs for cat vaccine, said will think about it                                                                                                                                                                                                                     </text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>0576F04C-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6ED774CF-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
Muffy re Revolution Promotion                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             </text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>0576F04C-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>BEA48C88-49FB-DF11-AF44-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Discussed the cat care pack letters that went out today.  They sent out over 300.  Will drop off stamps/additional loyalty cards at end of week.  Agreed that if 2 cats came in, the wud give them 2 free pipettes, 2 loyalty cards, but one pack.  Went over figures - looking good - over $15 in 2 months - and these have been their quietest months ever.  Will do a Revolution incentive every 3 months.  They need to increase sales month by month - every 3 months will get each clinic morning tea.  Cassie will do incentive form for their tea rooms by next Friday.  Talked about Campbell and the vaccines as we want to get them up and running with the postage paid postcards.  Robyn even admitted that the DHPPI will go off if Campbell is the only one using it and she wud stop buying it.  As they do A5 vaccine reminders, she will test putting in the annual health check pad sheet and the letter in a window envelope.  They will also look at getting a label printer for the postcards if they go that way.</text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>0587A60E-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>49AC17EC-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Pete doesn't work on Fridays so probably best to call on Thursday as although Joyce wold lobve to change purchasing Pete in charge.

use all norocarp now with no problems but rim injection.

Use clav 50mg and vetamox 625mg.  Have some old 500mg clav at full price although bought cheap.  Would prefer to use clav so will need to follow up with Pete.  Loved medicating leaflets and sent cat ones only.</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>0B53A02E-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>090EB523-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>started The Vet Club Rotorua March 09</text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>0D7ED08A-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>BBD7759D-F0C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Confirmed owed testing for 1200 dollars                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           
Call notes:     
Douwe Hoogstra has been sacked form the business which is great news leaving carin and Angela in charge. Ran through decto rebate and the subsidised testing that we owed them. Scabigard going extremley well this year with Ang swapping most farmers to scabigard                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                      </text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>0D7ED08A-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>0EFFC56E-B1A9-DE11-AF2D-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Bought starter pack for bulls. $ x Starter packs bought now, gave 200 mls free</text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>1264FDFA-8977-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>6405B523-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
Met with Dave Barton and Tom,
Rolled out Scourguard to them.
Dave really liked the look of the vaccine.
He said that the clinic would change over to it due to OSH,LUMPS,PRICE                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         </text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>1264FDFA-8977-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>5C4386FE-1D75-E011-AE34-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Tom Cat Roadshow at Novotel</text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>159F0423-8A77-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>C65CD623-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
end of year wrap up and wine drop                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 
Call notes:     
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          </text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>159F0423-8A77-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>C6C700AB-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>braekfast meeting reveiwed sales and lauched 2 &amp; 5 litre promo and talked about startect purchasing</text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>159F0423-8A77-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>84F42B20-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Called into see Karen, the scratch and win promo is going really well.</text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>2B39C980-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>0F576C71-16DC-4979-B6F3-9B1EE85881B2</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>went over new vv info, currently using at 5 mg/kg, so was interested in new dose rate.</text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>2B39C980-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>C48997DE-F1C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Go through Revolution straightener campaign after decline e-mail.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 
Call notes:     
TOOK IN COFFEE.  Had a meeting with Doris to again try to get them on board with campaign.  her main concern is that not only do they still have loads of stock from the Pet Expo, but it's not a big seller for them.  Finally agreed that they would get on board with campaign in December so that they can get through present stock ($3k order) and I will continue to do training.  Also went through proposal for all those going into cattery to get handout and offering Revolution pipette when purchasing a box for those cattery users.  Her head not in right space since knowing about Pet Doctors - agreed to bring up again next visit as i would like to get this done before the school holidays.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                       </text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>2B39C980-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>95F82B20-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
1.  To give them the confidence that OE is the product of choice and they will order it.
2.  Agreement on a farmer awareness campaign.
3.  Agreement that Rimadyl is the best pain relief                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                       
Call notes:     
Keen on promo of combo and a heifer TS day but using cheap Norbrook products.  probably only likely to go for Orbein DC with TS
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         </text>
	<date>2011-09-10 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>32FADE18-457C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>E10FED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>went over rim starter packs and video</text>
	<date>2011-09-10 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>32FADE18-457C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>973BAC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Stuart away for 3 months?

No one else available so left r detailer and said would follow up next call.</text>
	<date>2011-09-10 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>32FADE18-457C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>562AAC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>STILL GOING STRONG AT CLINIC BUT SALES BACK ON LAST SEASON, TOGETHR WITH MASTITIS IN GEN.</text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>34314E0E-8A77-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>898E36EC-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Revolution loyalty cards
REvolution =question card                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               
Call notes:     
went through the question card I made up for thier counter and staff eyes only, also replaced revfolution loyalty cards.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          </text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>34314E0E-8A77-E011-B6D6-001E101FE347</activity_id>
	<id>57D50113-BFF5-4FC8-BA99-7984A2C07BA3</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>see steve about database for dectomax</text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>39084B74-427C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>AFF7B423-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:

Convenia
Rimadyl                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               
Call notes:     

Phoned to  Cancel call -  vet to busy.

Will try to get appointment at 'Vets @ St Clair'

                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          </text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>39084B74-427C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>0326ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
F/up FTL
F/up new grad meeting that Ollie presented at
F/up pup classes                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         
Call notes:     
Spoke to Sharon as Janine was busy showing a new staff member around.  Sharon will be going on maternity leave in a few weeks.  Feedback from Ollie's presentation at the Vet Ent new grad meeting in Taupo is fantastic.  Will organise more pup classes resources.  FTL not happening as Sharon says that no-one has come in to ask for a kit.  I sent them 100 kits but Sharon said that they haven't got anything.  Will f/up where order has gone with Malcov</text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>39084B74-427C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>CFB800AB-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>has lepto under control order wise but will need more in new year, mainly 7 in 1.
Will get data projector organised &amp; down to clinic, he is away from 23rd dec.</text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>3E71204F-B46F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>714C9089-C889-4582-A5A2-56669099C08F</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Changing vax protocols and will do 2 yearly for dog and undecided on cat.  Looked at resp 2 and tis may fit but using f4 at presnet and John wants to move out with this.  Suggested use f4 as kitten vax and 1 a year later and then move out to 2.  Need to discuss with john.

Reviewed support material and delwyn will look at implementing.  use own vax cards as john does not like paspsort but delwyn liked idea of seperate plac efor aphc and vax.  also will use lables when need them.

Martha and Delwyn to speak to John.  matha likes passports and pads and wants to use.  catteries maybe a problem so will vax them annually.  Send out reminder annual so either use our card or change back to letter and include pad in it.  use IN for BB so need to cover this off next time.</text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>3E71204F-B46F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>06BE8C72-AAAE-4C04-A898-CF0AC75D4160</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>To detail calf vaccine run promotion</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>4826C44E-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>225ED623-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Detailed dectomax vaccine promo... some interest... doubt anything will come of it</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>4826C44E-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>F35FD623-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
meet with miranda, talk about a doing up a parasite management plan for the farm, is not going to be milking till next year,                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                      
Call notes:     
south coast dairies is still currently awaiting completed consences so at this stage will continue to be a dry stock farm until sometime next year, talked thru the different stock classes that are going to be run on the property and where dectomax will fit in for them, 
have done up a drench plan and emailed thru to miranda, she is interested getting other info put onto the drench plan ie:  when lepto shots, copper etc, she has meeting with justin muschamp on friday so after the meeting she will let me know when and where she wants the extra products put in.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                     </text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>4F04E33B-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>68099140-AB48-DE11-9725-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
clavulox and dermcare                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             
Call notes:     
detailed price change with clavulox, Justine would also like to do some more training on sales techniques and revolution, book for thursday night                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         </text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>4F04E33B-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>F7D62B20-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
Met with Tracy in regards to a farmer who vaccinated on the 23rd Dec for Sensortizor shot then has only just given booster shot(In calves)
I called Dr Phil in regards to this and he said to be on the safe side to give them another shot in 4 to 6 weeks time.
She contacted the farmer and he was happy to do this and said it had just slipped his mind in regards to booster shot.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                </text>
	<date>2011-09-22 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>522E99C8-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>98DE2B20-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Discussed rugby trip, sheep use of Dx and the Dingles! </text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>596D362D-417C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>B321ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Short call with Colin. Paul busy gave a run down of Dx. Seemed happy to try. Worked out he needs a Starter Pack. Not sure what he will do pre winter. Colin said he will follow up.</text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>596D362D-417C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>2626BBAD-CF7B-4BEE-8B39-566048B4A454</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
present revolution nurse promo winner to gail                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                     
Call notes:     
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          </text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>597FF649-3071-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6A17ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
checked stocks and see how cidr sales going                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                       
Call notes:     
ordered dectomax starter packs and cidrs above last years                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         </text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>597FF649-3071-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>17C200AB-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
revolution voucher promo                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          
Call notes:     
still not sell much at all and vets promote am but nirses trying with rev as think better.  Liked idea of getting reward and will keep clinic card as don't sell enough to get one each.

Michelle going to dental seminar.

Michelle Kirk left and gone to afterhours clinci and claire doing ordering etc                                                                                                                                                   </text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>5F93E1ED-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>79F055CF-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>organise dectomax for bull with orders he has recieved</text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>5F93E1ED-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>01A7B0A0-5905-42C6-B90A-3082D4A4C3BB</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>call to deatil new cydectin po offer and see what they would like to do around it etc - all good - Jason not to sure if fridge will be a goer - happy to look at a display etc </text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>638A2F19-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6B814820-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>dropped journal paper, need to use the cat and dog suites again - have ardered. clav drops have taken off and feels will have good rim winter - need to speak to russell re mailout.</text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>638A2F19-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>93E18B54-EDAD-4EF5-9901-351AE8BE47CA</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Has been using Genesis and is happy with the response and is looked after by Ancare.</text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>66784981-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>E7D255CF-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Had meeting with Rachel, discussed F2, currently on Intervet annually for cats and dogs, sees so-called "vaccination outbreaks" all the time, catteries pressure too.  Likes vaccinating yearly.  Would consider F2.  Talked about Mulit, needed to receive in post to read through.  Keen to read about advantages of revolution and use to recommend to clients.  Father unwell at present hence not focused.</text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>66784981-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>449517EC-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>leave copy of oa program materials with Eve, leave cytology detailer, all mailouts are done from sth end</text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>66784981-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6C22ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>revolution query, wanted me to replace just one rev card but advised needed to have 10 to redeem, was not happy about that as this would take them some time to do.  Said would hold the card to see what we could do.</text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>6CBAA23D-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>A121C00F-35A3-DF11-A251-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
To inform that current promo on 15 ltr ends today and detailed next months current promo with 2 &amp; 5 ltr                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           
Call notes:     
Spoke with Kim re cydectin PO - is happy with current stock levels so will pass on ordering any in at the good price. Wil look at ordering in some 2 &amp; 5 ltrs next week for promo. They dont make alot of sales in spring more autumn they have a big push.  Detailed statect and dropped startect tech detailers off but not a very big store for sheep                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  </text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>6CBAA23D-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>CAF0E8FF-42CC-DF11-B990-00A0C6000000</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>lstock ok on shelf ,sales down ytd sales going to going to bayer products as expiry on some products comming up</text>
	<date>2011-09-22 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>7193B1B2-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>BDF42B20-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Go over dx pour on, and build dx display                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          
Call notes:     
Kim interested in the Dx pour on costings, but still feels that genesis pour on is going to remain, particularly give nthe fact that he only has to pay for it in October.
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              </text>
	<date>2011-09-22 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>7193B1B2-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>8B13ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Farm calling with Maurice.</text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>7F1BBEBD-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>8AEA55CF-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Detailed Clav POA to Nicki, currently they use a lot of rilexine instead of amoxyocillin. Liked the pamphlets and will order when she next orders clav. Asked about the seperation of clav drops over time. She is finding that after about 9 days it seperates? (will follow up with Jen). Also sold in the Rimadyl atlas and Nicki ordered for July/Aug qualifying her for an atlas.</text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>7F1BBEBD-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>D2E267EA-2D5B-4EC5-83D2-FD8198DAA96E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>went through to answer machine</text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>8328A1A8-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>A817BD46-8F22-DE11-ABA5-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
meet and greet
sus out potential in clinic as per Catherine Archers request                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                      
Call notes:     
not in and didn't look like it was much of a LA clinic                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            </text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>8328A1A8-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>2800B98D-8FEE-4C0D-8139-0511C1DF6534</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Met with Jim Race to discuss incentive</text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>881CFBF2-427C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>D52FAC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>1500 x CCC vouchers,15x 2.5ltr, Coffee Machine, order.</text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>881CFBF2-427C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>D03BCD24-C360-4778-BDCA-C4D5C5C816AF</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Find out where to from here, regarding farm calling and dectomax sales                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            
Call notes:     
Kim needs some dx inj guns, so gave him 4 out of my bootstock.
Issues not resolved, but the demand for dectomax is there and it is still being sold in the mean time.
Quite happy for me to continue farm calling at present.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           </text>
	<date>2011-09-10 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>8FA10F40-457C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>5B2FED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Discuss bundling FIV with Brett and possibly look at Jackie's display board as an option.  Discuss Extended Care Card with Rimadyl.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               
Call notes:     
Went through FIV again.  He is not having much success, but I think it's got more to do with how he deals with it in consult.  Discussed focussing primarily on kittens, but he hasn't seen many this year.  Showed him the board that Jax made up, but if the posters haven't worked, then neither will this.  Suggested he change when he promotes vax, i.e. do first one when discussing not letting them decide and come back next visit.  Also went through Rimadyl detailer, and focussed on palatability and flexability and went through extended care card again.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                </text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>91398569-B46F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>F8EDA122-B62D-E011-B79D-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
convenia meeting with Northland NZVA, revolution                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
Meeting with Joyce re AGM finalise details, no invite has been sent out as yet, Joyce to email a copy and I can detail on m Northland trip, leave vax strategy, rev #4.  Still doing annual dog runs and wont be changing that at this point                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              </text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>91398569-B46F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>4A15ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>20 respisure needed. will be taking 20 a month.
would like to check out pricing for year.</text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>9BAB4E62-417C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>CE2AAC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Intro Mike to Alice and Discuss farm operation                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    
Call notes:     
Good catch up with Mike. Unfortunately he was busy loading cows, but still had a general chat with us. He is now down to 1 dairy farmer, and plans to have no heifers soon. Has a good amount of sheep and his own cattle now. Pretty wet, worried about an early winter. Hed been away to aussie on a house boat down the murray river.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  </text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>9BAB4E62-417C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6D1DED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
see kelv re uvac and bvd                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          
Call notes:     
wanted to try bvd vac on a herd that they are having problems with
took 30+ botts via svs
also organised 100+ packs of uvac 5in1 for raglan                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             </text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>A52E58BB-B36F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>E5A46DBD-CA8C-4772-8227-C0FD8C5797EE</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Wont' use Resp 2 - clinic mainly LV.  Gave Lena 3 cat packs.  Good to see that their Revolution is selling thru.  Explained that they were entitled to p/p postcards as she was trying to fit the normal postcard into a p/p envelope - ordered her 100.</text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>A52E58BB-B36F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>4977F046-5893-436D-AAB5-8A15255988D1</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
sort out lepto orders with clinic                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 
Call notes:     
spoke to guys re lepto
organised lepto and 7in1 for next year
will take around 40thousand doses of 2 way plus 12thousand 7 i n 1                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                </text>
	<date>2011-09-10 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>AF253224-457C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>A9C500AB-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>see jamie re scourgaurd

jamie cancelled left info</text>
	<date>2011-09-10 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>AF253224-457C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>AF874820-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Detail Scabigard and Ultravac 6 in 1                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              
Call notes:     
Two very differing opinions. Foxy very pro- scabigard, but Rae very " traditional" saying that farmers know Scabine and that it was a lot simpler. Hopefully Foxy can hold sway. Left leaflets, new applicator, dummy vial and scratch post on the front counter for her to encourage people to try the product.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          </text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>B0FC40D5-B36F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>9727ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
re confirm dectomax in sheep again this year                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                      
Call notes:     
Brian siad it was hard to tell how well it worked as it had been a good year last year anyway. I presented all details to him and he confirmed he would go again this year. yes 2000 ewes!!                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               </text>
	<date>2011-09-02 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>B0FC40D5-B36F-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>CEEEA4DE-CA63-DE11-973A-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
more interested in the drench bin he had left over that was accidentally sent to him!  Left it with Jenna for her to sort.
will use some teatseal but the diary market is not big for them.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              </text>
	<date>2011-09-15 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>BD399845-417C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>A4E42B20-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Revolution: sold in the peel &amp; win promotion.</text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>C532CCE8-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6AF1B423-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Father</text>
	<date>2011-09-17 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>C532CCE8-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>8CD5759D-F0C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>called into clinic dropped off teatseal material, spoke to darren all well at present. 15 buckets orderd.</text>
	<date>2011-09-16 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>CC0FCB68-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>E327AC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>spoke to matt about previcox again and samples, happy with rim and hasnt ordered any. also asked about vaccine presentation, has shown it to Jim who is considering the options. mentioned very happy with the service they have recieved from intervet and thats a big part of why they have stayed</text>
	<date>2011-09-23 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>DAD289DE-427C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>068C36EC-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
?Dog Runs
Follow up Domitor usage - Amelia further training 
New Vets?
Vaccine back to us?
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   
Call notes:     
Met with Amelia and Juan - both LA/SA vets - both leaving with Amie (from Eltham) to UK in December.  Discussed vaccine business - are they open to change from FD now part of STAHS?  Cost concious decision and discussed ext. duration options that may solve that for clients.  More concerned about cat owner compliance than dogs.    Gave me prices of FD at present and asked to quote, but no idea of volume.   Unsure why they use FD other than cost an</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>DE5FEA76-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>91EB55CF-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Discuss where Keith will be this week</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>DE5FEA76-407C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>25F1F52B-74FB-4E17-97FB-31B521CF49BD</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Call to fill clinic in on farm visits to date and see how sales are going                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         
Call notes:     
Sales slow - only two visits to date with more to confirm.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                </text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>E8AFE164-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>4817ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Mastalone levels.</text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>E8AFE164-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>DC3EAC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Parnell focus clearly change from treatment of whole herd into AA cows in the new repro season.  Ovsynch is clearly been positioned on price and convience to farm operators.  Two pricing structures in place at the moment a 100 cow vet pack at $780  and herd pack at $1480 which treats 250 cows.   Potential pricing to vet is $5.92 for AA cow treatment on the herd pack.  Some new NZ trial work, apparently completed in 2002, is to become available soon...??? which they have been speaking to vets about however at present seem to be hold it to themselves apparently until statitisical data is completed.</text>
	<date>2011-09-13 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>E8AFE164-0C75-E011-B6D4-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>9CAD3CD5-DE12-4E96-B6FC-36F27792C1C3</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
Present Ultravac SD 6 in  1, and spring dectomax                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  
Call notes:     
Loses very few lambs. They get 5 in 1, so feels that she has that pretty well covered.
Does not use any clostridials in her calves, but has only lost 1 in 10 years to what she thinks was a clostridial infection, so not likely to start treating her calves, unless that changes.
Will treat 192 x 80kg calves asap with Dx inj. Then in 2 months time give them a second dx inj when they get their copper bolus. They then go onto arrest c until early June, when they get another Dx inj. In September those animals get an arrest c coming out of winter as their pre-mate drench. Finally they get an arrest c the following Autumn. When they are teatsealed precalve then they will get a pour on.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           </text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>ED0D7AB6-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>CC2FED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
secure scabiguard business
intro Jared maloney
pick up secure vaccinator not going well                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         
Call notes:     
have a dedicated group of clients that use scabiguard
agreed that at times the scabine applicator can get runny and lose doses - that scabiguard is accurate
wil organise order within next week
selling scabiguard around 16c per dose - low margins
gave scratchpad and poster

now selling more 10in1 in sheep and farmers starting to respond to ewe lossessecure vaccinator not drawing - picked up
picked up dud secure vaccinator

small opportuni</text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>ED0D7AB6-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>610A428C-C78D-49CA-826B-5E274A1F9971</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Replaced stock of revolution cat - faulty. Discussed kitten packs - need to get in to see the vets as slightly concerned that the girls are giving out to all animates kittens who may not necessarily come back to the clinic.</text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>EE55B5A9-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>C0D155CF-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Wentr for a farm walk with Brenton to see calves we had tried dec pour on on. Calves were still very lose in back end and looked prtty average to be onest. left him with a fec teset and I will reccomend dec inj next time. Farm has history of miniral deficiency so he will check status in calves at same time. Picked up faulty pour on valve as well to do trial on with new gun.</text>
	<date>2011-09-09 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>EE55B5A9-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>6D62D623-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
To promote Pregsure through BMT                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   
Call notes:     
Good meeting with Rob.  If he did anything he would favour a simple approach of whole herd vaccination.  Send him my PP presination                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                       </text>
	<date>2011-09-22 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F0622AEC-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>9F13ED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>Transfer Dectomax injection for urgent sale.
Cheque clearence problem with finance dept.</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F1BF9C0E-E87A-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>8D30AC40-F3C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>nee Howser</text>
	<date>2011-09-21 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F1BF9C0E-E87A-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>893FF952-10DC-DE11-ADC0-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>call with NIna (TSR) RD1 Ngatea - discussedw why treating etc - he driven by price - will only get a 5.5litre if he buys - NIna will follow-up</text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F4B04B5F-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>1D834820-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>confirming an order for injection - 20 bottles with one aditional free - plus me spending a day out with David - happy with that </text>
	<date>2011-09-08 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F4B04B5F-447C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>98552E81-7D7D-DE11-81E4-444553544200</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>ASE comment                                             
Pre call objectives:
to see what dry cow proiducts they will be using this year                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                        
Call notes:     
do not use much of ours and will do much the same this year
using cheap Noraclox                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         </text>
	<date>2011-09-22 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F78D82D4-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>960FED4A-F2C3-E011-A0FF-00155D01180E</id>
</RECORD>
<RECORD>
	<text>re mastitis in the area, lots in hfrs, why?Haven't been suckled, not bagged up.</text>
	<date>2011-09-22 00:00:00</date>
	<activity_id>F78D82D4-437C-E011-B6D8-444553544200</activity_id>
	<id>5109FB5B-1F74-4565-BF22-A9B7D093F0FC</id>
</RECORD>
</RECORDS>
